{
    "question": "My study room..... beautiful\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>very</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kalo salahhhhh</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>is</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>my study room <u>i</u><u>s</u> beautiful</p><p>artinya</p><p>ruang belajarku indah</p><p></p><p>terimakasih</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "b-qsc-d-gl-i-have-a-favorite-bancherh-my-school-he-is-mr-denl-656",
            "question": "B    QSC\r\nD. GL\r\nI have a favorite bancherh my school He is Mr. Denl. He is\r\nmy English facher. He is 30 years old. He is tall and\r\nhandsome. He has round eyes a pointed nose, and thick lips\r\nHe has straight har that always looks neat. He is the strict\r\nand discipline person. He also has bng mustache and beard\r\nfairy dense. His sun is brown. He is very diligent. He is also\r\nsmart and honest He oves must very much. He is very good\r\nat playing a guitar. He is a good person and we bve him very\r\nmuch\r\n\r\n12. How does he look like?\r\nA He has found eyes a flat nose, and thin lips. He has\r\nstraight hair\r\nB He hasslanteyes a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has\r\nC. He has found eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He\r\nhas straight hair\r\nD. He has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thin lips. He has\r\ny hair\r\n13 How does he look like?\r\nA He has found eyes a fet nose, and thin lips. He has\r\nstraight hair\r\nB He has slant eyes a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has\r\nWavy hair\r\nC. He has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lps. He\r\nhas straight hair\r\nD. He has found eyes, a pointed nose, and thin lips. He has\r\n14.Deb\r\ncoo\r\nMrs\r\nis his skin brown?\r\nA Yes it's\r\nB No. is not\r\nC Yes. It does\r\nD. No. he is not\r\n15 What do you think about Mr. Dent?\r\nA He is very digort smart and honest person\r\nB Hois smart honest but lay person\r\nCHe is the strict but not discipline person\r\nD He is smart toucher but not discipline person\r\n16 A place where alrcraft magularly take off and land, with\r\nbuildings for passengers to waith\r\nA Gas Station\r\nB Train station\r\nC Arport\r\n17 Parking Ama many people standing outside the movie\r\nA There is\r\nB There are\r\nC There\r\nD Is there\r\n18 then a small cat playing with some toys\r\nA is\r\nB Are\r\nC Am\r\nD. Have\r\n19 We use this thing to cook our meals tsa\r\nA Basin\r\nB Stove\r\nC Rack\r\nD Knife\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>12. C. he has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has straight hair</p><p>13. C. he has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has straight hair</p><p>14. C. yes it does</p><p>15. A. he is very diligent, smart, and honest person</p><p>16. C. airport</p><p>17. B. there are</p><p>18. A. is</p><p>19. B. stove</p><p></p><p><strong>Semoga</strong><strong> </strong><strong>terbantu</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>maap</strong><strong> </strong><strong>kalo</strong><strong> </strong><strong>salah</strong><strong>\u270c</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-the-girls-are-watching-movie-in-the-cinema-547",
            "question": "2. (+)The girls are watching movie in the\r\ncinema.\r\n(-)..\r\n(?)...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(-) The girls aren&#039;t watching movie in the cinema</p><p>(?) Are The girls watching movie in the\n</p><p>cinema?</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "dimas-do-you-have-favorite-novels-rino-thave-two-favorite-novels-722",
            "question": "Dimas Do you have favorite novels?    Rino Thave two favorite novels. The llounted House\r\nand The Secret Place\r\nDimas What kind of novel are they?\r\nRino The Hounted House is a horror novel, and\r\nThe Secret Place is a detective story\r\nDimas Which one is thicker?\r\nRino \u00b7 The Haunted House has 50 pages, but the\r\nSecret Place has 75 pages,\r\nDimas How much did you buy those novels?\r\nRino : The Haunted House is Rp. 35.000, and The\r\nSecret Place is Rp. 125.000\r\nDimas: I like detective story, too. May I borrow yours\r\nsometimes?\r\nRino Certainly! You may come to my house because\r\nI have more interesting story books to read\r\n26. Who likes detective story?\r\nA Dimas.\r\nC None\r\nB. Rino\r\nD. Dimas and Rino\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Dimas </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>karena di situ  Dimas bilang \"i like detective story&#039;\"</p><p>maaf kalau salah ya, semangat belajar nya </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "w-o-b-l-i-n-g-a-good-word-is-tolong-dijawab-cepat-jangan-813",
            "question": "W-O-B-L-I-N-G . A good word is \u2026 *\r\nTolong dijawab cepat \r\njangan ngasal ngasal .....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>ini hurufnya diacak kan?</p><p>kalo disusun jadinya <strong>bowling</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>blowing</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "cerita-maling-kundang-dalam-bahasa-inggris-861",
            "question": "Cerita maling kundang dalam bahasa Inggris\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p></p><p>Long time ago, in a small village near the beach in West Sumatera, lived a woman and her son, Malin Kundang. Malin Kundang&#039;s father had passed away when he was a baby, and he had to live hard with his mother.</p><p></p><p>Malin Kundang was a healthy, dilligent, and strong child. He usually went to the sea to catch fish, and brought it to his mother, or sold it in the town.</p><p></p><p>One day, when Malin Kundang was sailing as usual, he saw a merchant&#039;s ship which was being raided by a small band of pirates. With his brave and power, Malin Kundang defeated the pirates. The merchant was so happy and asked Malin Kundang to sail with him. Malin Kundang agreed.</p><p></p><p>Many years later, Malin Kundang became a wealthty merchant, with a huge ship, loads of trading goods, many ship crews, and a beautiful wife. In his journey, his ship landed on a beach. The villagers reconigzed him, and the news ran fast in the town: Malin Kundang became a rich man and now he is here. His mother, in deepful sadnees after years of loneliness, ran to the beach to meet her beloved son again.</p><p></p><p>When the mother came, Malin Kundang, in front of his well dressed wife, his crews and his own gloriness, denied to meet that old, poor and dirty woman. For three times she begged Malin Kundang and for three times yelled at him. At last Malin Kundang said to her \"Enough, old woman! I have never had a mother like you, a dirty and ugly peasant!\" Then he ordered his crews to set sail.</p><p></p><p>Enraged, she cursed Malin Kundang that he would turn into a stone if he didn&#039;t apologize. Malin Kundang just laughed and set sail.</p><p></p><p>In the quiet sea, suddenly a thunderstorm came. His huge ship was wrecked and it was too late for Malin Kundang to apologized. He was thrown by the wave out of his ship, fell on a small island, and suddenly turned into stone.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: </p><p>hope yoy find this helpful^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-paragraf-dalam-kalimat-kalimat-yang-bentuk-present-perfect-253",
            "question": "Contoh paragraf dalam kalimat-kalimat yang bentuk present perfect tense\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Today is 16th August and tomorrow is my sister\u2019s birthday. Her name is Kristal. I want to give her a surprise. I have talked to some of her friends. They have helped me to prepare a surprising party. We have discussed it since July.</p><p>We are going to celebrate my sister\u2019s birthday in a small restaurant near my house. Our parents have also agreed it. The restaurant has been booked by our parents.</p><p></p><p>What about the birthday present? No worries, I have prepared it too. She loves art very much. I have made a painting for her. I hope she will like it. But I haven\u2019t wrapped the painting because it hasn\u2019t dried yet.</p><p></p><p>Have you ever celebrated someone\u2019s birthday?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "taj-mahal-of-india-isthan-candi-prambanan-of-indonesia-249",
            "question": "Taj mahal of india is...than candi prambanan of indonesia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Taj mahal of india is <strong>bigger</strong> than candi prambanan of indonesia</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban dicetak tebal dan menggunakan bentuk komparatif dengan kata sifat (Adjective) satu suku kata sehingga untuk membentuk komparatif harus ditambahkan akhiran -er, menjadi is bigger than. Jawaban tidak mutlak is bigger than, tetapi bisa juga is smaller than atau kata lain yang dianggap lebih sesuai dan lebih valid berdasarkan data pengukuran matematis.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "look-at-the-body-of-the-latter-can-you-find-the-following-items-957",
            "question": "Look at the body of the latter. can you find the following items    a. the date\r\nb. the time\r\nc. the contact for RSV\r\nd. the dress code\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D.Thw dress code</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-did-you-say-to-compare-animal-433",
            "question": "How did you say to compare animal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Bagaimana Anda mengatakan untuk membandingkan hewan</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>tuh artinya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>adalah hai</p><p> kamu namanya siapa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ana-arrange-the-words-to-be-good-sentence-me-delicious-gi-473",
            "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627    Arrange the words to be good sentence!\r\nMe - delicious - give - she-food - her\r\n4.\r\n5.\r\nBag is Rp 250.000\r\nWallet is Rp 150.000\r\nBag is..........\r\n..........than wallet ( expensive)\r\nWallet Is...........than bag (cheap)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>\u2022 She give me her delicious food.</p><p>\u2022 Bag is <strong>more </strong><strong>expensive </strong>than wallet.</p><p>\u2022 Wallet is <strong>cheaper </strong>than bag</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p></p><p>Susunlah kata-kata tersebut menjadi kalimat yang baik!</p><p>Saya - enak - beri - dia-makanan - dia</p><p>4.</p><p>5.</p><p>Tas seharga Rp 250.000</p><p>Dompet Rp 150.000</p><p>Tas adalah..........</p><p>..........daripada dompet (mahal)</p><p>Dompet Is...........daripada tas (murah)</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}